Sometimes, otherworlders come to this world.
Called the "Lost Ones," they possess special,
powerful abilities that have the potential
to distort the shape of the world itself,
known as Pure Concepts.
My job is to dispose of them before their
power has an impact on our world.
I'm a priestess: pure, just, and strong...
as well as an Executioner for exterminating Lost Ones.
According to Momo's information,
the target is in that building over there.
It's guarded heavily, as expected.
I could take them out,
but I don't want to cause a commotion if at all possible.
This outfit has been quite handy.
It's good for hiding my scripture, too. Good work, Momo.
I thought this might happen,
so I made this beforehand
with plenty of love in every stitch!
Although I do think she put a bit too much effort into it.
This should do it.
Invoke
Thread
She's the other Lost One.
The target I must execute tonight.
Episode 2: The Lost One
Are you the girl who came from another world?
Uh, yes!
I see...
Thank goodness!
What school and class are you from?
Nishibori High School, Class 1-3.
My name is Akari Tokitou.
Based on her answer, this girl's definitely my target.
Akari. Got it. I'm Menou.
I'm one of the Faust, of the first class.
"F-Faust"?
We can't let them see us.
Come inside.
Let's get you out of here, Akari.
Uh... What?!
Listen, Akari...
I heard about you from the other one.
"Other one"?
There was a boy who got summoned
from Japan the same time you were.
He found out what the Noblesse,
the ones who summoned you, were up to and ran away.
He came to my church for refuge,
but he was injured so badly I couldn't save him.
What?
But he still told me about you before he died.
That's why I want to save you, at least!
I know this story's full of holes,
but I can't give her time to think.
They said you have some kind of power, didn't they?
Y-yeah...
Apparently it's a power that can heal people's wounds.
The Noblesse plan to abuse that power.
Even if it's a power for healing,
they'll definitely find a way to use it for no good.
That's why we have to run. Right away!
I'm on your side, Akari.
Okay, I believe you.
They said you have some kind of power, didn't they?
Y-yeah...
Apparently it's a power that can heal people's wounds.
It sounds like her power isn't an aggressive one.
Then now's my chance,
while she still has her guard down.
Wait, what? Menou...?
Pure Concept [Time]
Invoke [Regression]
O-oooh, ow...
I-I think I tripped or something.
Oh. Hey, Menou!
Her wound disappeared?!
I'm sorry I'm such a clutz!
Did she heal it? No, that's not it. It's not just the wound.
We have to hurry and get out of here, right?
The bloodstains disappeared, too.
What is this? What is her power?
Could it be... the Pure Concept of Time?
Menou?
Momo!
Yes?
I'm taking the Lost One with me!
What do you mean? Didn't you kill her on the spot?
I'll explain properly later.
Go disrupt the guards on the east side!
Yes, ma'am.
I don't like the sound of this.
Hello there, stupid Noblesse! I'm a suspicious intruder!
An intruder! Get her!
We need to make a run for it, Akari!
Wh-what are we going to do, Menou?!
Uh, what?!
Menou-?!
Her Pure Concept won't let her die?
Yes, it's impossible to kill her with what I have on hand.
And you're sure her power isn't
"healing" but "time regression"?
Absolutely.
The Pure Concept that improperly attached
to her soul is most definitely that of Time.
That's a problem.
All Pure Concepts have disastrous potential, but Time...
Yes.
It might only revive her through regression for now,
but who knows how it will develop if it grows stronger?
The more one uses a Pure Concept,
the more it will eat away at the mind before
eventually taking over and raging out of control.
If her Pure Concept were to grow
stronger and get out of control...
The Sword of Salt that melted the
western continent into the sea.
The Pandemonium that devoured
the southernmost archipelago.
The Material Room that took over the
Wild Frontier in the east.
The Starhusk that carved out the center of
the northern continent and set it afloat.
Her power could cause a catastrophe worse
than even the Four Major Human Errors.
What should we do?
Don't worry.
Bring the otherworlder with you to where I am.
What? To Garm?
We have here...
a ceremonial hall that can eliminate any otherworlder.
Although we only use it in cases where
the Executioners can't manage.
Embarrassingly, I never knew of its existence.
Your Master Flare never once relied on my help,
so I assume she never told you, either.
Bring the otherworlder to me.
It will take me about three days to get the hall ready,
so get here by then.
Understood.
I'm grateful for the depth of your wisdom
and consideration, Archbishop.
I could do so much better, though.
Lately, there have been a series of young
women disappearing here in Garm.
I hate to think that I can't even save
the people who are within my reach.
Oh, but listen to me complain. I'm sorry.
Once you get to Garm,
let us have a nice long chat, Miss Menou.
The Lord is watching
Akari! Get up!
Wow!
Thank you, Menou!
Don't mind if I do!
Oh, you use chopsticks here.
Akari, keep eating and listen.
The Noblesse are definitely going to come after you.
This church isn't safe by any means.
Yeah, this church looks like it's about to fall down.
Like I explained earlier,
Lost Ones like you have special
powers we call "Pure Concepts,"
and that's what the Noblesse are after.
Hey, these omelet thingies are really good!
Can I have seconds?
Th-there aren't any more!
Look, Akari.
Even just the bodies of Lost Ones
can be used as magecraft material.
Some won't care if you're dead if
they can get their hands on you!
What, really? That's scary.
Right? That's why I'm thinking of relocating.
We're going to go to the ancient capital of Garm,
where our Church's cathedral is.
Ooh, a journey!
You and me,
setting off on a riveting adventure of escape!
What special feelings will develop between
the two along their lengthy journey?
It sounds like you're imagining something epic,
but it's just half a day and a bit by railroad.
What? Where's the romance in that?
That's what you're complaining about?
Anyway in Garm,
there's actually a ceremonial hall that can
be used to send otherworlders back home!
Then that means... I'm going back to Japan?
Exactly.
I spoke to the archbishop in Garm,
so you'll be able to go back in no time.
I see!
That's right!
But...
What's wrong?
I don't know.
I'm not sure why, but I suddenly felt really sad.
When I first met you, Menou,
I was startled of course,
but more than that it made me really, really, happy.
What?
I don't really understand it, either,
but for some reason it felt like...
time had started moving again after a long pause.
That the moment I'd been waiting for had finally arrived.
Wait, what? What's wrong with me?
You must think I'm really odd.
But Menou, I'm glad I got to come to this world.
I'm so glad I got to meet you.
You know what it is?
I'm pretty sure this is that thing they call fate!
When you put it that way,
I've got to say it feels pretty nice.
It should take a few days to prepare the ceremony,
so we can spend a bit more time together.
I hope we can be friends, Akari.
Uh-huh! I hope so too, Menou!
Here's the report.
They're going to officially put
King Grisarika on trial for heresy.
They'll begin as early as this afternoon.
I see.
This will make it hard for the Noblesse to do anything.
That's good for us.
Other than that,
seeing the breakfast I prepared for you chowed down
by Miss Boobalicious in there was really infuriating.
No one asked you to comment on that.
Let's just make quick work of her now!
It's true direct attacks might not do anything,
but what if we poison her gradually by-
No.
That might destroy her mind.
That kind of attack on someone possessing
a Pure Concept is taboo.
A Pure Concept is instable enough as it is.
There'll be a higher risk of it getting out of control.
I know that, but...
Repeated revival through regression is enough for
the Pure Concept to develop into a greater risk.
That's why we can't try killing her in
ways that don't have good odds.
All right?
Fine.
So, did you get what I asked for?
For starters, I have clothes and stuff in here.
And here are the railroad tickets.
Express Train Third Class Ticket
From Grisarika Central Station
to Garm Station
Express Train Second Class Ticket
From Grisarika Central Station
to Garm Station
Thank y-
Momo?
Didn't I say your job was to remain
here and join in on the trial?
I'd rather die first!
In case something happens,
it will be better if Akari doesn't know you exist.
You realize that, don't you?
If it means leaving you alone with the likes of her,
I'd rather kill King Grisarika and force the trial
to end so that I can catch up with you!
Oh come on, Momo.
That girl is dangerous!
My instinct is blaring sirens that I should
never leave the two of you alone together!
Hey, I know how dangerous that girl could b-
No, you don't understand at all!
You've never had to spend significant
time with a target before, you know?
That's true, but-
I don't think you're suited for that kind of thing.
So I want you to trade places with me!
Starting now, just leave her up to me-
I can't.
Why not?!
"Why"...?
To have to kill someone who hasn't
violated a taboo or committed a crime,
who's just an ordinary, nice person...
That's my job. That's why.
Then here's what I'll do.
I'll tag along stealthily so that
Boobalicious doesn't notice.
Momo!
I'm coming, and that's final!
Okay, fine...
Just make sure you don't run into her by accident.
Honestly, you're way too worried about this, Momo.
I'm only going to be with Akari for a few days.
I won't give myself away.
I'm not worried about you giving yourself away.
Hey, Menou! You're back!
Menou?
Sorry for the wait, Akari.
I went and got some clothes for you.
Something's going on at the castle,
and there aren't many guards around right now.
We'll set off as soon as you're changed.
Okay!
Ooh.
Whoa.
Wow!
When you said "station,"
I imagined the ones in Japan,
but this is much more exciting than I thought!
I feel like a tourist!
I'm glad you're happy with it.
It's so pretty! What is this stuff?
They're particles of etheric light.
The trains in this world run on ether.
"Ether"?
Yes.
Ether, the guiding force.
Ether
It's the foundation of our world's civilization.
It's generated from people's souls as well,
but there are larger sources like
earthen veins and heavenly veins.
It's also the power that drives magecraft.
Magecraft
"Magecraft"? Is that like magic?
I think it's a little different.
Magecraft is a type of technology,
for controlling and composing ether.
Does that mean anyone can use it?
Theoretically, yes.
But you need specialized tools and training,
and above all, a talent for it.
Statistically, there are more people who can't use it.
Akari, your ability to use magecraft without tools
or training makes you a special kind of genius.
A "genius"?! Wow, I'm a genius?!
Don't get carried away, now.
Listen, Akari...
Don't be careless about using magecraft.
People are after you right now.
You can't do anything that attracts attention.
All right. I hear you, Miss Menou.
I'll buy us something to eat on the way.
An extravagant boxed lunch or something would be nice.
I don't have the money for that.
Aww!
Mommy!
Mommy?!
Are you lost?
Are you okay?
Yup.
What a good girl! You're not crying! So strong!
Oh, you scraped your palm.
Let's see...
Here's your change.
Thank you.
Knights from the castle?
Are they looking for Akari?
No, that's unlikely.
They seem to be looking for something,
but they don't have a sense of urgency.
As long as we stay inconspicuous until they're gone...
Now, let's make that owie...
Akari!
If she uses that magecraft now,
she'll attract their attention!
Invoke
Bubble
What's this?!
Who would do this in here?
Is it a prank?
What's going on?
So pretty!
Take that!
Menou, what's with the karate chop?
I told you not to attract attention, didn't I?!
What?
It's okay, these bubbles are getting all the attention.
I'll have you know I had to make these myself!
What?! You did this, Menou?!
You shouldn't attract attention with magecraft!
Don't give me that!
Hey.
Did you make these, Miss? You're amazing!
It really isn't that amazing.
It uses the crest on this coin,
and it's a pretty basic conjuring.
Oh, but I can control the movement
of the bubbles to some extent,
so I guess that part's kind of cool.
So amazing!
Is it?
Express, Ancient Capital No. 7
For Garm
First Class, Carriage 1
I'm so sorry for the trouble.
Oh, it wasn't any trouble at all!
Come on, let's get on.
Bye!
Yup, bye-bye!
See you!
I guess they're going to Garm as well.
Well, we should board, too-
What?
Hmm? Nothing.
I just thought you showing off
back there was kind of cute.
I wasn't showing off...
You don't have to be embarrassed!
Keep this up, and you'll regret it.
Ooh, I'm so sorry!
That dang Boobalicious...
Getting all friendly with my Menou!
Wait, isn't that...?
Princess Ashuna!
What are you two doing here?
We came looking for Your Highness, of course!
How could you leave at a time like this,
when His Majesty is dealing with the trial?!
I'm not my father. He can take care of himself.
But I didn't imagine I'd get caught this soon.
Uhhh, she thought she could get away dressed like that?
That's princess logic for you...
Come, let's get you back.
By the way, what do you think of these bubbles?
Just a prank, probably?
It's harmless magecraft.
A prank, eh?
Where to?
I'm heading for Garm. That's why I'm here.
Then we shall accompany you!
Wow, this is so great.
It really feels like we're off on a journey!
Isn't this exciting, Menou?!
Yes, it is.
Go ahead and enjoy the trip, Akari.
Because when this journey ends, the thing that awaits...
...is the end of your life.
Next Episode
Taboo in [Red]
Next episode: Taboo in [Red].